	7012 Skylane Dr, Orlando, FL 32819	\Diamond
l •	(516) 510-1604	C
Alvin	alvinkpollard@gmail.com	
Pollard		

Artist and programmer who has created several video games as part of an indie development duo. Exceptional communicator who can bridge the gap between art and engineering. Expert at building and managing relationships at all levels across an organization; creative, innovative, and collaborative. Committed to continuous learning and building competency in tech tools. Game samples:

- Game on Steam: The Concourse
- Games on itch.io: Epic Brick Battle, West Indian Dominoes Simulator, Boulder Scroll Shears

Skills

• (UI feature development	•	Motion graphics and animation
• (Graphic Design	•	After Effects
• 9	Shader graph systems	•	3D Digital Content Creation

Experience

SEPTEMBER 2015 - PRESENT

Partner / A&B Game Studios, Orlando, FL

- Utilize 2D and 3D art packages to create indie video games
- Mastery of fundamental 3D concepts, both understanding and application of modeling, texturing, rendering, shading, lighting, rigging, skinning, dynamics, particle systems
- Extensive knowledge of the node-based visual programming via Unreal Engine, including creating and trouble-shooting blueprints; familiar with Unity and C#
- Profile game performance and apply art optimization

MAY 2013 — SEPTEMBER 2015

Freelance Artist / Self Employed, Orlando, FL

- Created medical animation videos that showcased the use and functionality of a medical device
- Utilized Premiere, After Effects and Photoshop to created logos, presentations, and videos for client Pop.Earth, a non-profit organization that serves children with developmental disabilities

JUNE 2011 - MAY 2013

Admissions Representative / DAVE School, Orlando, FL

- Met with prospective students to answer application questions, host tours, conduct interviews and plan orientation events
- Created marketing collateral, web banner ads, and print ads to promote the school
- Animated, modeled and composited assets for multiple productions

OCTOBER 2008 - JUNE 2010

Global IT Consultant / Esteé Lauder, Melville, NY

- Ensured company-wide PCI compliance/network security (both nationally and internationally) through the review of existing documentation and by creating new documents for firewalls
- Collaborated with three teams to troubleshoot and resolve security issues
- Served as liaison between IT department and business units

Education

JUNE 2011

Diploma in Digital Animation and Visual Effects / DAVE School, Orlando, FL